export const chapter = "Chapter - 22: Industrial Regions and Major Industries ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "Which factors contribute to the development of industrial regions?",
        optionA: "Availability of raw materials and manpower",
        optionB: "Good weather and scenic landscapes",
        optionC: "Access to tourist attractions",
        correctAnswer: "A) Availability of raw materials and manpower",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In which type of countries are agro-based industries chiefly located?",
        optionA: "Developed countries",
        optionB: "Developing countries",
        optionC: "Both developed and developing countries",
        correctAnswer: "B) Developing countries",
      },
      {
        question: "Why are primary industries often located near coalfields?",
        optionA: "To reduce transportation costs",
        optionB: "To be closer to seaports",
        optionC: "To benefit from skilled labor",
        correctAnswer: "A) To reduce transportation costs",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Industries dependent on import of raw materials and export of finished goods are usually set up near:",
        optionA: "Agricultural regions",
        optionB: "Seaports and river-ports",
        optionC: "Mountainous areas",
        correctAnswer: "B) Seaports and river-ports",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is NOT one of the four major industrial regions in the world mentioned in the text?",
        optionA: "Western and Central Europe",
        optionB: "Eastern Asia",
        optionC: "Southern Africa",
        correctAnswer: "C) Southern Africa",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In which country is the Ruhr Valley of India, also known as the Chotanagpur Region, located?",
        optionA: "India",
        optionB: "China",
        optionC: "Russia",
        correctAnswer: "A) India",
      },
      {
        question: "Which country has the largest iron ore reserves?",
        optionA: "China",
        optionB: "India",
        optionC: "Brazil",
        correctAnswer: "C) Brazil",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the primary industry mentioned in the text that forms the basis of a country's development and progress?",
        optionA: "Information technology industry",
        optionB: "Cotton textile industry",
        optionC: "Iron and steel industry",
        correctAnswer: "C) Iron and steel industry",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which city in India is referred to as the 'Cottonopolis of India'?",
        optionA: "Mumbai",
        optionB: "Chennai",
        optionC: "Ahmedabad",
        correctAnswer: "C) Ahmedabad",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In which Indian city has the IT industry earned the epithet 'Silicon Valley of India'?",
        optionA: "Chennai",
        optionB: "Bengaluru",
        optionC: "Hyderabad",
        correctAnswer: "B) Bengaluru",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "The Industrial Revolution in the __________ century in Europe changed the face of the world.",
        options: ["17th", "18th", "19th"],
        correctAnswer: "18th",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The process of manufacturing was divided into several steps, each of which was dealt by a different __________ and worker.",
        options: ["craftsman", "machine", "supervisor"],
        correctAnswer: "machine",
      },
      {
        question:
          "A large-scale industry operates on a very large scale in terms of investment, range of market, transportation, work force, and energy, such as the __________ industry.",
        options: ["toy", "textile", "iron and steel"],
        correctAnswer: "iron and steel",
      },
      {
        question:
          "An industry requires a regular and assured supply of __________ material, especially a large scale industry using heavy and bulky raw material.",
        options: ["finished", "raw", "processed"],
        correctAnswer: "raw",
      },
      {
        question:
          "An industry cannot be set up at any place you feel like; several favourable factors have to be looked at before an industry is set up at a place or in a particular __________.",
        options: ["region", "sector", "product"],
        correctAnswer: "region",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In terms of ownership, industries can be classified into several types, one of which is the __________ industry, such as Tata Motors Ltd, Godrej Group, and Reliance Industries.",
        options: ["public sector", "private sector", "joint sector"],
        correctAnswer: "private sector",
      },
      {
        question:
          "A cottage industry is a small industry, chiefly run by a few people, like the members of a family; it produces goods at a very small scale, and it procures raw materials from local sources and supplies the finished goods in the local market. Normally, it does not involve much __________ and many modern machines.",
        options: ["of specialization", "division of labor", "technology"],
        correctAnswer: "of specialization",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The means of transport is an important factor if the raw materials or finished goods are bulky and heavy. A place well connected by efficient roadways, railways, waterways, and airways is preferred for setting up an __________.",
        options: ["industry", "enterprise", "agricultural farm"],
        correctAnswer: "industry",
      },
      {
        question:
          "A developed country is called so because it has attained a high degree of industrial development, which also brings economic development and __________.",
        options: ["recession", "depression", "prosperity"],
        correctAnswer: "prosperity",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What kind of industry is typically associated with small-scale production, a one-time investment in machinery, and a large workforce?",
        options: [
          "cottage industries",
          "large-scale industries",
          "small-scale industries",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "small-scale industries",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Agriculture is directly related to food security.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question: "The world population is growing at about 1.1% per year.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "With the growing population, agricultural land is expanding.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Modern ways of living have led to a reduction in food wastage.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The use of chemical fertilizers and pesticides has a positive impact on soil fertility.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Industrial Revolution in the 18th and early 19th centuries had no significant impact on agriculture.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question: "India is traditionally an industrial country.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The government introduced land reforms to redistribute land among landless laborers.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Indian farmers primarily use organic fertilizers in their farming practices.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The government has not taken any steps to address the problems associated with agriculture.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
